Spencer Brown Spirited dreamer, radical pragmatist.

Bio

"Hi, I'm Spencer, a passionate entrepreneur with a dedication to driving the future of technology. I'm currently directing the organizing team behind BoilerMake, Purdue's 500-student hackathon with over \$200,000 in funding. Outside of tech, I'm interested in contemporary architecture, hip hop, and philosophy."

Technical Skills

EXPERIENCE Ruby/Rails HTML CSS Java Python

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING SKILLS

Git/git flow, TDD, pair-programming, Agile, Vim, Sublime Text, *nix

FAMILIAR TECHNOLOGIES

Javascript (jQuery, AngularJS, node), Bootstrap, Heroku, AWS

Projects

SPENDING.ME

September 2014 - PennApps Hackathon

Created a Rails app that leverages the Plaid and Venmo APIs to show a complete overview of actionable spending data for Venmo users. Won the "That's Crazy, Man" prize.

LODGE

August 2014 - Y Combinator Hackathon

Built a Rails app that connects users with Facebook friends of friends to find lodging when traveling.

BOILERMAKE REGISTRATION (2x)

January 2014, July 2014

Built Rails apps to service hackathon participants, sponsors, and organizers. Handled registration, team formation, and user permissions.

STUDY HUB

September 2013 - August 2014

Developed a Rails app that empowered Purdue students to collaborate on study guides in real-time with Etherpad-Lite. A prototype design attracted over 85% of Purdue's 260+ honors engineering freshmen to register as

Education

PURDUE UNIVERSITY HONORS COLLEGE

B.S., Computer Science,

Certificate in Entrepreneurship and Innovation (May 2017)

- · GPA: 3.88/4.00
- Presidential Scholarship Recipient, 2x Dean's List, 2x Semester Honors

Work Experience

CONTINUITY CONTROL

Software Engineering Intern (May 2014 - August 2014) Worked as a full-stack web developer in an Agile environment where the team pair-programmed exclusively.

DENISON UNIVERSITY

Research Assistant (July 2013 - August 2013)

Progressed toward establishing a reproducible method for creating reliable TiO2-based, dye-sensitized solar cells.

EXALTED COLLECTIBLES

Co-Founder (June 2012 - July 2013)

Co-founded an online trading card retailer that drew over 2,000 unique customers in 2013.

Community Engagement

CS UNDERGRADUATE STUDENT BOARD

Member (March 2014 - Present)

Advancing Purdue's CS department by acting as the liaison between students, faculty, and corporate partners.

SIGMA TAU GAMMA FRATERNITY

Member (February 2014 - Present)

Striving to improve the image of fraternal life at Purdue by maintaining a high standard of character.

BOILERMAKE

Director (September 2013 - Present)

Leading the organization of a hackathon at Purdue with 500+ students and \$200,000+ in funding.

PURDUE ENTREPRENEURSHIP CLUB

Director (August 2013 - Present)

Stimulating entrepreneurship across campus with competitions, events, and workshops.

PURDUE HACKERS

Vice President, Outreach (August 2013 - Present)

Driving hacker culture at Purdue through club events and activities.